<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SuperGymer</string>
    <string name="menu_plan">Plan</string>
    <string name="menu_user">Me</string>
    <string name="menu_scan">Scanner</string>
    <string name="title_activity_android_sqlite_tutorial">AndroidSQLiteTutorialActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pat">patActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="dumbbell_name">Dumbbell</string>
    <string name="yoga_name">Yoga mat</string>
    <string name="treadmill_name">Treadmill</string>
    <string name="part_arm">arm</string>
    <string name="part_chest">chest</string>
    <string name="part_abdomen">abdomen</string>
    <string name="part_reduce_fate">reduce fat</string>
    <string name="part_leg">leg</string>
    <string name="dumbbell_arm_introduction">Muscle: Brachiordialis\nHow to use:\nStep 1: Stand with feet about hip-width apart, abs engaged as you hold medium heavy dumbbells in front of the thighs. Squeeze the biceps and bend the arms, curling the weights up towards the shoulders.\nStep 2: Keep the elbows stationary and only bring the weight as high as you can without moving the elbows. Slowly lower the weights, keeping a slight bend in the elbows at the bottom (e.g., don\'t lock the joints and try to keep tension on.</string>
    <string name="dumbbell_chest_introduction">Muscle: pectoralis\nHow to use:\nStep 1: This exercise is very similar to the regular barbell bench press except that you will be using an incline free weight bench press machine and your upper chest will be the muscle group worked instead of your middle chest.\nStep 2: Lift the dumbbell off of the rack and slowly lower it to about 3 inches above your clavicle (just below your Adam\'s apple) and then press bar back to the start position. DO NOT TOUCH YOUR UPPER CHEST (this causes unneeded shoulder joints and takes the tension away from your upper pec muscles, which are what want to doing the work!). that when you are lowering the dumbbell that you do in a slow and controlled fashion. Conversely, when you press the dumbbell upward, you want to do so in an explosive fashion.</string>
    <string name="dumbbell_abdomen_introduction">muscle: Rectus Abdominis\nHow to exercise\nStep 1: Lie down on the floor. Wrap weight around upper body with your arms. Keep knees bent and feet flat on floor.Step 2: Raise your upper body upward while keeping your lower back on the floor. Hold for one second. Return to starting position.</string>
    <string name="yoga_abdomen_introduction">Muscle: rectus abdomins\nStep 1: While lying on your back, Straighten your legs, raise your heels an inch off the floor, and place your hands by your sides.\nStep 2: Keeping your arms parallel to the floor, lift your torso and legs so they form a e. As you raise yourself, bend your knees and pull them up toward your chest.</string>
    <string name="yoga_leg_introduction">Muscle: Glutes\nStep 1: Stand with your feet shoulder width apart. Lift your stronger or dominant leg straight out in front of your, as high as possible.\nStep 2: Such air into the stomach, then push your hips back and squat down as far as possible while keeping your torso as upright as possible. The heel of your front leg can touch the floor at the bottom of the squat, if you can get down that far.\nStep 3: Return to the starting position and exhale. Do all your repetitions with your non dominant leg, then repeat with your dominant leg.</string>
    <string name="treadmill_reduce_fat_introduction">Tips:\n1. Do not stop during your running, keep running until last minutes.\n2. Try to running in the morning because the glycogen level is lowest in your body and therefore you can gain a better result of fat reduced .\n3. warm-up exercise is necessary, do not ignore it!</string>
    <string name="h">/Users/qingzhi/AndroidStudioProjects/SuperGymer/app/src/main/res/drawable/btdevice_treadmill.png</string>


    <string name="player_error">Error initializing YouTube player: %s</string>
    <string name="seek_to">Jump To</string>
    <string name="seek_to_hint">Seconds</string>
</resources>
